<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<GateDocument>
<!-- The document's features-->
<GateDocumentFeatures>
<Feature>
  <Name className="java.lang.String">gate.SourceURL</Name>
  <Value className="java.lang.String">C:\Users\waage\Documents\MI-DDW\homework1\myGateExample\extracted_train_neg.xml</Value>
</Feature>
<Feature>
  <Name className="java.lang.String">MimeType</Name>
  <Value className="java.lang.String">text/html</Value>
</Feature>
</GateDocumentFeatures>
<!-- The document content area with serialized nodes -->
<TextWithNodes>
<Node id="0" />
Story of a man who has unnatural feelings for a pig. Starts out with a opening scene that is a terrific example of absurd comedy. A formal orchestra audience is turned into an insane, violent mob by the crazy chantings of it's singers. Unfortunately it stays absurd the WHOLE time with no general narrative eventually making it just too off putting. Even those from the era should be turned off. The cryptic dialogue would make Shakespeare seem easy to a third grader. On a technical level it's better than you might think with some good cinematography by future great Vilmos Zsigmond. Future stars Sally Kirkland and Frederic Forrest can be seen briefly.
<Node id="1" />
Airport '77 starts as a brand new luxury 747 plane is loaded up with valuable paintings &amp; such belonging to rich businessman Philip Stevens (James Stewart) who is flying them &amp; a bunch of VIP's to his estate in preparation of it being opened to the public as a museum, also on board is Stevens daughter Julie (Kathleen Quinlan) &amp; her son. The luxury jetliner takes off as planned but mid-air the plane is hi-jacked by the co-pilot Chambers (Robert Foxworth) &amp; his two accomplice's Banker (Monte Markham) &amp; Wilson (Michael Pataki) who knock the passengers &amp; crew out with sleeping gas, they plan to steal the valuable cargo &amp; land on a disused plane strip on an isolated island but while making his descent Chambers almost hits an oil rig in the Ocean &amp; loses control of the plane sending it crashing into the sea where it sinks to the bottom right bang in the middle of the Bermuda Triangle. With air in short supply, water leaking in &amp; having flown over 200 miles off course the problems mount for the survivor's as they await help with time fast running out...Also known under the slightly different tile Airport 1977 this second sequel to the smash-hit disaster thriller Airport (1970) was directed by Jerry Jameson &amp; while once again like it's predecessors I can't say Airport '77 is any sort of forgotten classic it is entertaining although not necessarily for the right reasons. Out of the three Airport films I have seen so far I actually liked this one the best, just. It has my favourite plot of the three with a nice mid-air hi-jacking &amp; then the crashing (didn't he see the oil rig?) &amp; sinking of the 747 (maybe the makers were trying to cross the original Airport with another popular disaster flick of the period The Poseidon Adventure (1972)) &amp; submerged is where it stays until the end with a stark dilemma facing those trapped inside, either suffocate when the air runs out or drown as the 747 floods or if any of the doors are opened &amp; it's a decent idea that could have made for a great little disaster flick but bad unsympathetic character's, dull dialogue, lethargic set-pieces &amp; a real lack of danger or suspense or tension means this is a missed opportunity. While the rather sluggish plot keeps one entertained for 108 odd minutes not that much happens after the plane sinks &amp; there's not as much urgency as I thought there should have been. Even when the Navy become involved things don't pick up that much with a few shots of huge ships &amp; helicopters flying about but there's just something lacking here. George Kennedy as the jinxed airline worker Joe Patroni is back but only gets a couple of scenes &amp; barely even says anything preferring to just look worried in the background.The home video &amp; theatrical version of Airport '77 run 108 minutes while the US TV versions add an extra hour of footage including a new opening credits sequence, many more scenes with George Kennedy as Patroni, flashbacks to flesh out character's, longer rescue scenes &amp; the discovery or another couple of dead bodies including the navigator. While I would like to see this extra footage I am not sure I could sit through a near three hour cut of Airport '77. As expected the film has dated badly with horrible fashions &amp; interior design choices, I will say no more other than the toy plane model effects aren't great either. Along with the other two Airport sequels this takes pride of place in the Razzie Award's Hall of Shame although I can think of lots of worse films than this so I reckon that's a little harsh. The action scenes are a little dull unfortunately, the pace is slow &amp; not much excitement or tension is generated which is a shame as I reckon this could have been a pretty good film if made properly.The production values are alright if nothing spectacular. The acting isn't great, two time Oscar winner Jack Lemmon has said since it was a mistake to star in this, one time Oscar winner James Stewart looks old &amp; frail, also one time Oscar winner Lee Grant looks drunk while Sir Christopher Lee is given little to do &amp; there are plenty of other familiar faces to look out for too.Airport '77 is the most disaster orientated of the three Airport films so far &amp; I liked the ideas behind it even if they were a bit silly, the production &amp; bland direction doesn't help though &amp; a film about a sunken plane just shouldn't be this boring or lethargic. Followed by The Concorde ... Airport '79 (1979).
<Node id="2" />
This film lacked something I couldn't put my finger on at first: charisma on the part of the leading actress. This inevitably translated to lack of chemistry when she shared the screen with her leading man. Even the romantic scenes came across as being merely the actors at play. It could very well have been the director who miscalculated what he needed from the actors. I just don't know.But could it have been the screenplay? Just exactly who was the chef in love with? He seemed more enamored of his culinary skills and restaurant, and ultimately of himself and his youthful exploits, than of anybody or anything else. He never convinced me he was in love with the princess.I was disappointed in this movie. But, don't forget it was nominated for an Oscar, so judge for yourself.
<Node id="3" />
Sorry everyone,,, I know this is supposed to be an "art" film,, but wow, they should have handed out guns at the screening so people could blow their brains out and not watch. Although the scene design and photographic direction was excellent, this story is too painful to watch. The absence of a sound track was brutal. The loooonnnnng shots were too long. How long can you watch two people just sitting there and talking? Especially when the dialogue is two people complaining. I really had a hard time just getting through this film. The performances were excellent, but how much of that dark, sombre, uninspired, stuff can you take? The only thing i liked was Maureen Stapleton and her red dress and dancing scene. Otherwise this was a ripoff of Bergman. And i'm no fan f his either. I think anyone who says they enjoyed 1 1/2 hours of this is,, well, lying.
<Node id="4" />
When I was little my parents took me along to the theater to see Interiors. It was one of many movies I watched with my parents, but this was the only one we walked out of. Since then I had never seen Interiors until just recently, and I could have lived out the rest of my life without it. What a pretentious, ponderous, and painfully boring piece of 70's wine and cheese tripe. Woody Allen is one of my favorite directors but Interiors is by far the worst piece of crap of his career. In the unmistakable style of Ingmar Berman, Allen gives us a dark, angular, muted, insight in to the lives of a family wrought by the psychological damage caused by divorce, estrangement, career, love, non-love, halitosis, whatever. The film, intentionally, has no comic relief, no music, and is drenched in shadowy pathos. This film style can be best defined as expressionist in nature, using an improvisational method of dialogue to illicit a "more pronounced depth of meaning and truth". But Woody Allen is no Ingmar Bergman. The film is painfully slow and dull. But beyond that, I simply had no connection with or sympathy for any of the characters. Instead I felt only contempt for this parade of shuffling, whining, nicotine stained, martyrs in a perpetual quest for identity. Amid a backdrop of cosmopolitan affluence and baked Brie intelligentsia the story looms like a fart in the room. Everyone speaks in affected platitudes and elevated language between cigarettes. Everyone is "lost" and "struggling", desperate to find direction or understanding or whatever and it just goes on and on to the point where you just want to slap all of them. It's never about resolution, it's only about interminable introspective babble. It is nothing more than a psychological drama taken to an extreme beyond the audience's ability to connect. Woody Allen chose to make characters so immersed in themselves we feel left out. And for that reason I found this movie painfully self indulgent and spiritually draining. I see what he was going for but his insistence on promoting his message through Prozac prose and distorted film techniques jettisons it past the point of relevance. I highly recommend this one if you're feeling a little too happy and need something to remind you of death. Otherwise, let's just pretend this film never happened.
<Node id="5" />
"It appears that many critics find the idea of a Woody Allen drama unpalatable." And for good reason: they are unbearably wooden and pretentious imitations of Bergman. And let's not kid ourselves: critics were mostly supportive of Allen's Bergman pretensions, Allen's whining accusations to the contrary notwithstanding. What I don't get is this: why was Allen generally applauded for his originality in imitating Bergman, but the contemporaneous Brian DePalma was excoriated for "ripping off" Hitchcock in his suspense/horror films? In Robin Wood's view, it's a strange form of cultural snobbery. I would have to agree with that.
<Node id="6" />
The second attempt by a New York intellectual in less than 10 years to make a "Swedish" film - the first being Susan Sontag's "Brother Carl" (which was made in Sweden, with Swedish actors, no less!) The results? Oscar Wilde said it best, in reference to Dickens' "The Old Curiosity Shop": "One would have to have a heart of stone not to laugh out loud at the death of Little Nell." Pretty much the same thing here. "Interiors" is chock full of solemnly intoned howlers. ("I'm afraid of my anger." Looking into the middle distance: "I don't like who I'm becoming.") The directorial quotations (to use a polite term) from Bergman are close to parody. The incredibly self-involved family keep reminding us of how brilliant and talented they are, to the point of strangulation. ("I read a poem of yours the other day. It was in - I don't know - The New Yorker." "Oh. That was an old poem. I reworked it.") Far from not caring about these people, however, I found them quite hilarious. Much of the dialog is exactly like the funny stuff from Allen's earlier films - only he's directed his actors to play the lines straight. Having not cast himself in the movie, he has poor Mary Beth Hurt copy all of his thespian tics, intonations, and neurotic habits, turning her into an embarrassing surrogate (much like Kenneth Branagh in "Celebrity").The basic plot - dysfunctional family with quietly domineering mother - seems to be lifted more or less from Bergman's "Winter Light," the basic family melodrama tricked up with a lot of existential angst. It all comes through in the shopworn visual/aural tricks: the deafening scratching of a pencil on paper, the towering surf that dwarfs the people walking on the beach. etc, etc.Allen's later "serious" films are less embarrassing, but also far less entertaining. I'll take "Interiors." Woody's rarely made a funnier movie.
<Node id="7" />
I don't know who to blame, the timid writers or the clueless director. It seemed to be one of those movies where so much was paid to the stars (Angie, Charlie, Denise, Rosanna and Jon) that there wasn't enough left to really make a movie. This could have been very entertaining, but there was a veil of timidity, even cowardice, that hung over each scene. Since it got an R rating anyway why was the ubiquitous bubble bath scene shot with a 70-year-old woman and not Angie Harmon? Why does Sheen sleepwalk through potentially hot relationships WITH TWO OF THE MOST BEAUTIFUL AND SEXY ACTRESSES in the world? If they were only looking for laughs why not cast Whoopi Goldberg and Judy Tenuta instead? This was so predictable I was surprised to find that the director wasn't a five year old. What a waste, not just for the viewers but for the actors as well.
<Node id="8" />
This film is mediocre at best. Angie Harmon is as funny as a bag of hammers. Her bitchy demeanor from "Law and Order" carries over in a failed attempt at comedy. Charlie Sheen is the only one to come out unscathed in this horrible anti-comedy. The only positive thing to come out of this mess is Charlie and Denise's marriage. Hopefully that effort produces better results.
<Node id="9" />
The film is bad. There is no other way to say it. The story is weak and outdated, especially for this country. I don't think most people know what a "walker" is or will really care. I felt as if I was watching a movie from the 70's. The subject was just not believable for the year 2007, even being set in DC. I think this rang true for everyone else who watched it too as the applause were low and quick at the end. Most didn't stay for the Q&amp;A either.I don't think Schrader really thought the film out ahead of time. Many of the scenes seemed to be cut short as if they were never finished or he just didn't know how to finish them. He jumped from one scene to the next and you had to try and figure out or guess what was going on. I really didn't get Woody's (Carter) private life or boyfriend either. What were all the "artistic" male bondage and torture pictures (from Iraq prisons) about? What was he thinking? I think it was his very poor attempt at trying to create this dark private subculture life for Woody's character (Car). It didn't work. It didn't even seem to make sense really.The only good thing about this film was Woody Harrelson. He played his character (Car) flawlessly. You really did get a great sense of what a "walker" may have been like (say twenty years ago). He was great and most likely will never get recognized for it. As for Lauren, Lily and Kristin... Boring.Don't see it! It is painful! Unless you are a true Harrelson fan.
<Node id="10" />
This film is one giant pant load. Paul Schrader is utterly lost in his own bad screenplay. And his directing is about as comatose as it can be without his actually having been sleepwalking during the process. The worst though is Woody Harrelson, whom I ordinarily like when he's properly cast. He plays "the walker", a homosexual man in D.C. who plays social companion to the bored wives of the Washington elite. He couldn't have been more one dimensional if he had been cut out of a magazine and bounced around in front of the camera on a popsicle stick. His "southern accent" is that "off the rack" version that decrescendos from the beginning to the end of every line he delivers, as though the heat and humidity of the South is still draining him of every ounce of energy he has. It is monotonous. But, his is not the worst accent in the movie. His "boyfriend", played by Moritz Bleibtreau, attempts to affect some kind of a Mid East accent that is so clumsy he can barely deliver the bad lines written for him. He is incapable of rolling his r's in spite of the fact that in real life he is German, and speaks several languages - one of them being Italian! That's kind of a good reason to cast someone else don't ya think? From the story, to the screenplay, to the directing, to the camera work, to the performances by the leads, this movie is bad from beginning to end. The only tolerable moments in this film came from three supporting actresses: Lily Tomlin, Lauren Bacall, and Kristin Scott Thomas. Only these three managed to make it through this movie with their dignity in tact. In fact, all three are excellent, in spite of being trapped in a really bad film. Ufortunately, no one could ever be good enough to redeem this endless series of flaws. If you like these three actresses, watch them in something else. This movie is not worth your time.
<Node id="11" />
The plot for Descent, if it actually can be called a plot, has two noteworthy events. One near the beginning - one at the end. Together these events make up maybe 5% of the total movie time. Everything (and I mean _everything_) in between is basically the director's desperate effort to fill in the minutes. I like disturbing movies, I like dark movies and I don't get troubled by gritty scenes - but if you expect me to sit through 60 minutes of hazy/dark (literally) scenes with NO storyline you have another thing coming. Rosario Dawson, one of my favorite actresses is completely wasted here. And no, she doesn't get naked, not even in the NC-17 version, which I saw.If you have a couple of hours to throw away and want to watch "Descent", take a nap instead - you'll probably have more interesting dreams.
<Node id="12" />
Plot is not worth discussion even if it hints at corruption, murder, power and the rest of thriller related topics. Characters are interesting though sometimes. Not realistic but interesting nevertheless.Development is slow like tea drinking ceremony. Visuals not stunning, but good enough to ease the eye strain. Good movie to watch after dinner before going to bed - nothing shocking too much, nothing overexciting. Movie sitcom style.I liked Woody - excellent performance. Had to fight the plot inadequacy and did the job pretty good. The rest are bearable though very predictable. The whole is watchable and better than most TV shows.
<Node id="13" />
This film is about a male escort getting involved in a murder investigation that happened in the circle of powerful men's wives.I thought "The Walker" would be thrilling and engaging, but I was so wrong. The pacing is painfully and excruciatingly slow, that even after 40 minutes of the film nothing happens much. Seriously, the first hour could be condensed into ten minutes. That's how slow it is.The fact that it lacks any thrills or action scenes aggravates the boredom. It's almost shocking that even argument scenes are so plain and devoid of emotion. Maybe it is because of the stiff upper lip of the higher social class? It's sad that "The Walker" becomes such a boring mess, despite such a strong cast. Blame it on the poor plot and even worse pacing.
<Node id="14" />
This movie must be in line for the most boring movie in years. Not even woody Harrison can save this movie from sinking to the bottom.The murder in this movie are supposed to be the point of interest in this movie but is not, nothing is of any interest. The cast are not to bad but the script are just plain awful , I just sat in utter amazement during this movie, thinking how on earth can anyone find this movie entertaining The producers of this movie were very clever. They made a boring movie but hid it well with the names of good actors and actresses on their cast. People will go to the blockbuster and probably see this movie and think, Woody Harrison ,Kristin Scott Thomas and Willem Dafoe this must be good and rent this movie.(boy are they in for a horrible time)If you like getting ripped off go and rent this movie, some people actually did enjoyed this movie but I like to watch a movie with meaning
<Node id="15" />
A worn-out plot of a man who takes the rap for a woman in a murder case + the equally worn-out plot of an outsider on the inside who eventually is shut out.With such an outstanding case, one would think the film would rise above its hackneyed origins. But scene after scene drones by with no change in intensity, no character arcs, and inexplicable behavior.The homosexuality theme was completely unnecessary -- or on the other hand, completely unexplored. It seemed to be included only to titillate the viewers. When will Hollywood learn that having gay characters does not automatically make a more compelling picture?A regrettably dreadful movie. When will Lauren Bacall pick a good one? I expected better of her and Kristin Scott Thomas. This one is definitely one to miss.
<Node id="16" />
I saw this movie at a drive-in in 1959. Until "Howard the Duck" I considered this the worst movie I had ever seen. This movie tried to combine all the genera in one; comedy, horror, teenage angst, and the hot rod that must have sired "My Mother, The Car." Maybe it deserves a second viewing to see if it is an accurate reflection of it's time.
<Node id="17" />
Ghost of Dragstrip Hollow is a typical 1950's teens in turmoil movie. It is not a horror or science fiction movie. Plot concerns a group of teens who are about to get kicked out of their "hot rod" club because they cannot meet the rent. Once kicked out, they decide to try an old Haunted House. The only saving grace for the film is that the "ghost" (Paul Blaisdell in the She Creature suit) turns out to be an out of work movie monster played by Blaisdell.
<Node id="18" />
"Ghost of Dragstrip Hollow" was one of the many '50s movies about hot-rodding teens encountering the supernatural. In this case, the teens can't pay the rent for their hangout and get evicted. With nowhere else to go, they decide on an apparently haunted house. As you may have guessed, once they arrive, some weird things start happening. And there's a twist at the end.There's nothing in this movie that you haven't seen in other movies, but it's nice entertainment nonetheless. My favorite character was the foul-mouthed parrot. Well, let me rephrase that: he didn't talk like a character in a Quentin Tarantino movie, but he said things that we don't expect out of a bird. The movie's pure hokum, but harmless.
<Node id="19" />
"Ghost of Dragstrip Hollow" appears to take place in a spotless netherworld, an era long gone by, where the biggest sin a kid could commit would be in defying the law and getting a traffic ticket. It opens with a young female auto fanatic getting the business from her arch rival, who pressures her into a car race. That's about it for the drag-racing--this B-flick is mostly concerned with rock 'n roll, man! The folks at American International were obviously fond of decent, square teens who liked to party and yet didn't mind an adult chaperone. There are a few amusing double entendres and fruity exchanges (Necking Kid: "We thought we'd come out for some fresh air"...Dad: "Where did you think you'd find it, down her throat?"), but the ghost is a little late in arriving. Brief at 65 minutes, the movie cheats us with a climactic car race that actually takes place off-screen and a pre-"Scooby Doo"-styled unmasking which makes no sense. However, for nostalgia buffs, some mindless fun. ** from ****
<Node id="20" />
The characters are unlikeable and the script is awful. It's a waste of the talents of Deneuve and Auteuil.
<Node id="21" />
Kareena Kapoor in a bikini hmmmmmmmm.Akshay Kumar...Anil Kapoor....Maybe Saif....Kareena Kapoor in a bikini.....Good Banner..Kareena Kapoor in a bikini.....Not one good reason not to see this movie....Or so i thought ........Didnt these people make JBJ...Why o Why did i forget that.For all the criticism the first half of the movie isn't that bad...There is some intrigue and YOU FEEL A SORT OF IRRITATION MIXED WITH EXCITEMENT THAT I FELT WHEN SEEING GUY RITCHIE MOVIES LIKE LOCK STOCK AND SNATCH.Kareena Kapoor is sizzling in a very skinny model sort of way.Akshay Kumar is Akshay Kumar as only he can be.Anil Kapoor is annoying but kind of funny, YOU ALMOST FORGET THAT MOST OF THE TIME YOU CANNOT UNDERSTAND HIM.Saif is sidey ala Main Khiladi.. once again.There is the occasional laugh and a few chuckles, and a few goosebumps during the kareena-saif love story (kareena in the rain, behind me on my bike hmmmmmmm).BUT MOSTLY THIS HALF PROMISES MORE THAN IT DELIVERS.....WHICH MAKES THE SECOND HALF ALL THE MORE UNBEARABLE....There was almost a cheer when the interval came not only because because of the wet kareena because of what people thought were the things to come.INSTEAD WE WERE TREATED TO MIND NUMBING TORTURE WHICH IS DIFFICULT TO PUT IN WORDS.Saif suddenly seam like a comic sidekick...SUDDENLY THE SEXY KAREENA LOOKS ANOREXIC, YOU REALISE THAT THE SECOND LAST FLOOR IS NOW EMPTY AND HER FACE LOOKS TO BIG FOR HER BODY ( only girls can notice this and make other guys notice the second last floor was my observation).ANIL KAPOOR AND HIS SIDEKICKS GET ON YOUR NERVES.Akshay Kumar is the only one who carries off the madness to some extent but even he become intolerable after a while.ALL THE WHILE YOU ARE SUBJECTED TO ONE ABSURDITY AFTER THE OTHER.WHY??!! WHAT??!!! WHEN?!!! WHERE?!!! WHAT HAVE I DONE TO DESERVE THIS...A collective gasp went trough the audience before every song in the second half, which were ordinary even without the movie around it.Cannot relieve the trauma anymore....CONCLUSION.THIS MOVIE STARTS OF AS A BUZZ WHICH YOU FEEL COULD EVEN TURN OUT TO A HIGH BUT ENDS UP SLOWLY MOVING TOWARDS A HEADACHE AND THEN RAPIDLY TURNS INTO A FULL BLOWN MIGRAINE ATTACK.Please don't watch this movie for any reason other than academic interest.+s Cast, Akshay Kumar, first half.+/-s what, when, how, who to much confusion.(need a book to fill this).+s cast, the whole second half (need many pages to fill this).total 3/10 (im trying to avoid the 1s and 2s too not seem to extreme but make no mistake this movie is unwatchable no matter how decent the first half is).
<Node id="22" />
I rented this on DVD and I kind of feel bad since Dawson and Lugacy are so earnest about it in the DVD comments. It's not a bad movie exactly, but it's one of those films that desperately wants to be a deep comment on human nature while not realizing that its story is practically a genre. Plus, it is a little simplistic about the issue in a lot of ways, and the characters' behavior often strains belief. I'd say its a film that you would get something out of if you don't have a lot of film/TV/literature/life behind you (to be honest, I've seen almost exactly the same story in horror comics even). Otherwise, its point has been made before and more artfully. And that gets to the big problem, which is that it really doesn't have much of cinematic interest to it besides the point. It ends up being a fairly bland movie overall that invests everything in the idea that the basic story will be shocking and compelling, and it doesn't really pay off.
<Node id="23" />
Vijay Krishna Acharya's 'Tashan' is a over-hyped, stylized, product. Sure its a one of the most stylish films, but when it comes to content, even the masses will reject this one. Why? The films script is as amateur as a 2 year old baby. Script is king, without a good script even the greatest director of all-time cannot do anything. Tashan is produced by the most successful production banner 'Yash Raj Films' and Mega Stars appearing in it. But nothing on earth can save you if you script is bland. Thumbs down! Performances: Anil Kapoor, is a veteran actor. But how could he okay a role like this? Akshay Kumar is great actor, in fact he's the sole saving grace. Kareena Kapoor has never looked so hot. She looks stunning and leaves you, all stand up. Saif Ali Khan doesn't get his due in here. Sanjay Mishra, Manoj Phawa and Yashpal Sharma are wasted.'Tashan' is a boring film. The films failure at the box office, should you keep away.
<Node id="24" />
The worst movie I have seen since Tera Jadoo Chal Gaya. There is no story, no humor, no nothing! The action sequences seem more like a series of haphazard Akshay Kumar Thumbs-Up advertisements stitched together. Heavily influenced from The Matrix and Kung-Fu Hustle but very poorly executed.I did not go a lot of expectations, but watching this movie is an exasperating experience which makes you wonder "What were these guys thinking??!!".The only thing you might remember after watching it is an anorexic Kareena in a bikini.The reason why I did not give a rating of '1' is that every time I think I have seen the worst, Bollywood proves me wrong.
<Node id="25" />
</TextWithNodes>
<!-- Named annotation set -->
<AnnotationSet Name="Key">
<Annotation Id="0" Type="comment" StartNode="0" EndNode="1">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">3</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="1" Type="comment" StartNode="1" EndNode="2">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">4</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="2" Type="comment" StartNode="2" EndNode="3">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">4</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="3" Type="comment" StartNode="3" EndNode="4">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">1</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="4" Type="comment" StartNode="4" EndNode="5">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">1</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="5" Type="comment" StartNode="5" EndNode="6">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">3</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="6" Type="comment" StartNode="6" EndNode="7">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">3</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="7" Type="comment" StartNode="7" EndNode="8">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">4</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="8" Type="comment" StartNode="8" EndNode="9">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">1</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="9" Type="comment" StartNode="9" EndNode="10">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">2</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="10" Type="comment" StartNode="10" EndNode="11">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">1</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="11" Type="comment" StartNode="11" EndNode="12">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">4</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="12" Type="comment" StartNode="12" EndNode="13">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">3</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="13" Type="comment" StartNode="13" EndNode="14">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">3</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="14" Type="comment" StartNode="14" EndNode="15">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">1</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="15" Type="comment" StartNode="15" EndNode="16">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">1</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="16" Type="comment" StartNode="16" EndNode="17">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">2</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="17" Type="comment" StartNode="17" EndNode="18">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">2</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="18" Type="comment" StartNode="18" EndNode="19">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">4</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="19" Type="comment" StartNode="19" EndNode="20">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">4</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="20" Type="comment" StartNode="20" EndNode="21">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">3</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="21" Type="comment" StartNode="21" EndNode="22">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">3</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="22" Type="comment" StartNode="22" EndNode="23">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">4</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="23" Type="comment" StartNode="23" EndNode="24">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">3</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
<Annotation Id="24" Type="comment" StartNode="24" EndNode="25">
  <Feature>
    <Name className="java.lang.String">rating</Name>
    <Value className="java.lang.String">2</Value>
  </Feature>
</Annotation>
</AnnotationSet>
</GateDocument>
